♪ ♪
(birds chirping)
- (water trickling)
- (birds continue chirping)
BOY: Mm-mm.
(both laughing)
(boy speaks Hindi)
(makes slurping sound)
(low, muffled shouting)
TIGER:
There are no fucking rules!
Fight!
- (dings)
- (crowd cheering)
(shouting in Hindi)
♪ ♪
(body blows)
(groans)
(crowd cheering)
(crowd continues
shouting in Hindi)
(both grunting)
(shouting continues in Hindi)
(cheering)
(panting)
(grunting)
Sir, Tiger, sir.
CROWD (chanting): King Kobra!
King Kobra! King Kobra!
WOMAN:
Tiger, I love you!
CROWD (chanting):
King Kobra! King Kobra!
Whoo!
- Good evening.
- (groaning)
That's what I'm talking about.
Welcome to Tiger's Temple.
This is a sacred space.
Because some of us here
are Muslim.
Some of us are Hindu.
Fuck, maybe there's
a closet Christian
hiding somewhere there
under the rafters.
(booing)
But we here all worship one god:
the Indian rupee!
(crowd cheering)
The winner,
the killer of the beast,
- King Kobra!
- (cheering)
Look at this maderchod.
Look at this.
That's the smell of victory
right there.
- Do you smell it?
- ("King Kobra" chant continues)
'Cause I fucking smell it!
(fading):
This is a champion. This is...
- (muffled shouting)
- ("King Kobra" chant fades)
♪ ♪
(breathing heavily)
(grunts, spits)
(continues breathing heavily)
(match strikes)
TIGER: Fucking hell, guys.
What a night, eh?
(sniffs)
You hear that?
They fucking hate you.
It's incredible.
What a night.
Sarishan,
what's this fucking stomach?
Too many samosas.
You're the Lizard King,
not the fucking
Samosa King, okay?
This fucking tap!
Aziz, the fucking tap came off
in my hands again, man.
Come here.
Look here. What's that?
That fucking stays on. You know
what my water bill is for that?
Fix the fucking tap. Please.
I ask just for a little bit
of fucking cleanliness.
A little bit of
personal hygiene. Yes, what?
(sniffs)
Yeah. All right.
Don't spend it all at once, eh?
Tiger. Tiger, this is half.
What? That's what
you got last time.
What, are you saving
for a better place to live?
You want another 50%,
you bleed.
That's why it's called
the bleed bonus.
I need that money.
Then dance.
Don't look at me like that.
You chose the name.
You're like
those little monkeys,
you know, in the marketplace
that go...
(imitates screeching monkey)
with a little pink skirt.
That's you.
Put on a show, get the money.
There's hundreds
of folks out there
that'll do this, eh--
hundreds--
waiting to take your place
if this isn't for you.
REPORTER (over TV):
Baba Shakti.
Guru, man of peace,
the nation's lion.
Born to poverty
but not held captive by it.
Indeed, Baba Shakti is now
likely to be seen
in the temples of the elite
than at the temples
of the gods,
rubbing shoulders
with the rich and powerful.
Are these the simple actions
of a man made good...
BABA SHAKTI: I leave politics
to the politicians.
REPORTER: ...or the start
of a push for political power
through his endorsement
of the controversial
Sovereign Party?
If I see a God-fearing man
who is doing good for India,
I will support him.
REPORTER: He has dismissed
rumors that his factory...
First class, bro.
Eh! Make it a double.
So?
Lucky, Lucky, Lucky.
LUCKY:
This is who you want.
Queenie Kapoor,
the queen of Kings.
Friday afternoon,
she had a massage
and pedicure at Body Tonic.
Most of the mornings,
she stops at
a Café d'Italia for coffee.
D'Italia?
Yeah.
She'll be there tomorrow.
BABA SHAKTI:
Ayurvedic wisdom
Okay.
is thousands of years old.
Good job.
Who are we
to question the gods?
QUEENIE: Yes.
On the dinner table,
it was like
a verbal contract.
(speaking Hindi)
I don't have any mail.
QUEENIE: Yeah. I don't
have any... any mail...
Please, please, madam.
(Queenie shouts in Hindi)
I'm... Ow!
(glass shatters)
(man speaking Hindi)
Oh, my God.
How can you allow
these guys here?
What kind of a place
are you running?
("151 Rum" by JID playing)
♪ Run, Ricky, run, run
Run, jump, jump, come ♪
- ♪ Here they come
Run, run, run, run ♪
- (man shouts)
- (child shouts)
- ♪ Gun with the drum
Bum bitty bum ♪
♪ Slump in the trunk
My city go ♪
♪ Dumb, dumb, dumb, dumb
151 rum and a blunt ♪
♪ Young ... numb, numb, numb
And he got a little gun ♪
♪ A little bitty killer
Really doin' it for fun ♪
♪ Give him a little bit
And he'll get a ... done ♪
- (jovial chatter, laughter)
- ♪ Son of a god, son of a... ♪
♪ Son of woman and man, son of
a son, in a sunken abyss ♪
♪ Summon a plan
Please come with a script ♪
♪ Cover my back, cover man
Please come with the blitz ♪
♪ Look at the stats
JID like a magician ♪
♪ This some real-ass ... ♪
♪ I paid blood for this ♪
♪ Taking cheese
From the government ♪
♪ Cereal boxes
With the bugs in it ♪
♪ Hand-me-down
This my brother brother ♪
♪ Run, Ricky, run
Run, run, jump ♪
(calling in Hindi)
♪ Jump, come, here they come
Run, run, run, run ♪
♪ Gun with the drum
Bum bitty bum ♪
♪ Slump in the trunk
My city go ♪
(child speaks Hindi)
♪ Dumb, dumb, dumb, dumb
151 rum and a blunt ♪
♪ Young ... numb, numb, numb
And he got a little gun ♪
♪ A little bitty killer
Really doin' it for fun ♪
♪ Give him a little bit
And he'll get a... ♪
(music stops)
♪ ♪
(siren wailing in distance)
(quiet chatter)
(scanner beeping)
- (chatter in Hindi)
- (scanner beeping)
(busy chatter)
(knocking)
Madam?
QUEENIE: Yeah?
Where did you find this?
Some men were fighting
over it next to, uh, JV Road
near Café d'Italia.
I tried to rush in,
and, uh, um...
they fought back and, uh...
Take this.
I-I...
I don't... (chuckles)
I don't want charity.
Wh-What I need is a...
is a job.
This is Kings.
We just don't hire
off the street.
Where's your references?
Your CV? Hmm?
(cell phone vibrating)
Look, I don't have time
for all this.
This.
There's my CV.
That's bleach.
Chemical, oil.
Give me the job
no one wants to do.
I'll do it.
No complaint.
This is all I know.
(cell phone vibrating)
(speaks Hindi)
Yeah.
No. Uh, no, no. Listen.
I actually liked this one
from Indonesia.
Is she broken in?
No, th-that's fine,
but I just want to know
if, uh...
How quickly
can we get her papers?
Hmm?
(heavy, shaky breathing)
(lighter clicks)
Anyone who talks
outside these walls,
anyone who forgets their place,
it doesn't turn out
well for them.
Understood?
Understood.
(train rattling and screeching)
(gasps)
(bell jingling)
(busy chatter)
ALPHONSO:
New guy, huh?
What's your name?
Bobby.
ALPHONSO:
Hmm.
Wear your cap properly.
We don't want one of your pubes
in the curry... (speaks Hindi)
Bobby.
I think we met before, right?
I-I don't think so.
You like tequila,
huh, Bobby?
Patrón, Don Julio,
the one with
George Clooney in the photo?
I just want to clean
the dishes, okay?
Coke? Morphine? MDMA?
Oi, Alphonso, eh,
I've told you many times
to stop hassling my staff.
Quality control, man.
(speaking Hindi)
You're gonna thank me
for this one day.
Stay cool, Bobby.
Stay cool, hmm?
(Alphonso shouts in Hindi)
Watch my fucking leg, man.
(panting, grunting)
(announcement in Hindi
playing over speakers)
- (lively chatter)
- (announcement continues)
(lively chatter continues)
(boy speaking Hindi)
Paan.
(chuckles)
(door opens)
(door closes)
Is this all you got?
Yeah.
(sighs)
Are you sure?
'Cause I got an answer
to every prayer.
You like John Wick?
'Cause this just came in.
(laughs)
Yeah.
The TTI.
Same gun from the movie.
But made in China.
(exhales sharply)
Boom.
(gun clicks)
I want something small
but effective.
...38 caliber revolver.
It's a little bit heavy,
but it's got a lot of thump.
You need to be pretty close.
BOBBY:
Close is good.
I'll take it.
(scanner beeping)
(traffic sounds)
Staff entrance. Copy.
MAN (over radio): Copy.
Staff entrance secured.
(beeps, lock clicks)
(Queenie speaking angrily
in Hindi)
QUEENIE: Huh?
Huh?
- (Sita sniffling)
- Okay, okay. Don't cry.
(cell phone vibrating)
Yeah?
You're fucking killing me,
Rahul.
- (snaps fingers)
- No, no, no. Uh-uh.
Listen to me... (speaks Hindi)
You call Evgeni
and tell that motherfucker
to find another source.
They're fuck all. Fuck all.
Fuck all.
You understand "fuck all"?
No, no, no. No, no.
Listen, listen.
I have a reputation to protect, understand?
What the fuck is your problem?
How many times
do I have to tell you
fucking knock on the door
and enter... (speaks Hindi)
Sorry.
Nishit said you needed me.
QUEENIE: I need you
to learn some manners,
you inbred little goat fucker.
Rahul,
I'll have to call you back.
Listen, go to Naqeeb
and pick up some
Kashmiri snowflake.
Good stuff, okay?
None of that cheap shit.
But the problem is, uh,
quality control, it's no good.
Naqeeb has some issue with me,
you know?
I don't know whether
it's the Christian-Muslim thing
or what, but...
Hey.
- (snaps fingers)
- You. Face the wall.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
- Tell Naqeeb,
if the maal is good,
- (keypad beeping)
we'll buy some more
for Chief Rana.
Get it sorted by the weekend.
He is coming with his boys.
Hey, Alphonso.
Hmm?
QUEENIE: Only the best to
serve the VIPs.
(door closes)
ALPHONSO: Yeah. Got it.
(keypad beeping)
Alphonso. Alphonso.
Hey, uh, good job with Queenie,
huh? She really respects you.
What do you want?
Um, look, if you...
if you...
Look, if you need any help
with the VIPs...
(woman speaks indistinctly)
Look, I'm just saying,
if you need someone to go in
and do the job...
Does it look like
I need some help
from someone like you?
- Hey.
- Is there-- What the fuck, man?
Okay, okay. I'm sorry.
Look, you want to
make some money?
Guaranteed?
Go on.
Okay.
Uh... come to
this place tonight.
(paper rustling)
Bet on Khan.
You'll make a killing.
(chuckles)
How the fuck do you know?
I-I'll be fighting him.
(chuckles)
(laughing)
Fuck off.
The monkey will win
the first two rounds
and go down in the third.
What's in it for you?
I want a promotion.
("Maushi" by Sneha Khanwalkar
and RADA playing)
♪ What the fuck did you say,
Maushi? ♪
♪ Kay bolli? Kay bolli? ♪
♪ What the fuck did you say,
Maushi? ♪
- (cheering)
- ♪ Kay bolli? ♪
♪ Are mavshi chi gaand ♪
♪ Chehra bagh nantar bhaand ♪
♪ Maazi makdachi jaat zaaloy
Khulla sand ♪
♪ Vikun khau shakto tuze akkhe
Ghar daar aik zara ♪
- ♪ Ani Old monk chi quarter ♪
- Drill him! That's it! Nice!
♪ Bolta bolta bottle zaali ♪
♪ Jara daman
Padshyal khaali! ♪
♪ Bhakkam sharir pan fakt ata
Hadke rahli ♪
- ♪ Tari dokyavar madke
Bhari kaa ♪
- Kill him, boy!
- ♪ Karan roz chi zhavzhav ♪
- Yes!
♪ An dochkyala tras... ♪
TIGER: Get it!
(music stops)
(breathing heavily)
(muffled shouting)
(high-pitched ringing)
(crowd chanting indistinctly)
(breathing shakily)
Drill him!
Don't just stand there!
Get back, drill him!
Hit me! Hit me!
(grunting)
Harder!
Come on! Harder! Hit me!
TIGER:
Don't just stand there, mate!
Give him some of that Kong shit.
(heavy, distorted breathing)
Fucking yes! Fucking yes!
(crowd cheering)
(bell dinging)
Fuck yes! Whoo!
You fucking beauty!
Mwah! (laughs)
Get this fucking monkey
off here.
Guys, get the monkey off here.
The winner,
the killer of the beast,
Sher Khan!
- (cheering)
- (dinging)
(bell dings, door closes)
♪ I don't care
Who's wrong or right ♪
♪ I don't really wanna fight
No more ♪
♪ Too much talking, babe... ♪
- (elevator bell dings)
- (song stops)
("I Believe in Love"
by Polyrhythmics playing)
Make sure the drinks
never dry up.
Eyes to the ground
unless someone calls you,
then you will get over there
like you got
a chili up your asshole.
You see that?
That's the defense minister.
He always has a mushroom steak
followed by a threesome.
(chuckles): This one
just likes to watch.
But he's the head
of the tax office,
so anything is allowed,
you know?
A very good evening,
Mr. Gupta.
Hope you are having
a good time.
Enjoy.
Filthy bastard.
♪ Come on, people
Do you believe in love? ♪
♪ You gotta stand for something
Or you'll fall for anything ♪
♪ I said, come on, people... ♪
ALPHONSO (chuckling): You're
looking beautiful today, huh?
Hey... (speaks Hindi) You see
those yellow fellas over there?
That's Mr. Takahata.
He always asks Queenie
for the special menu.
We've got girls
from all over the world, man.
Dubai, Russia, Singapore.
There's a dish
to please every king. Look.
He's about to receive
a gift from heaven.
(bell dings,
elevator door opens)
Here she is-- Sylvia.
Former Miss Lithuania.
(laughs)
She's come down
to guide him to the afterlife.
Come on. That's Mirza.
The boss of the bosses.
He runs everything
in this town, man.
Drugs, property, import, export.
You name it.
What about the cops?
They're the dirtiest fuckers.
You know what I'm meaning.
And Chief Rana?
ALPHONSO:
Up in the VIP room.
He loves the sugar.
(engine revving)
ALPHONSO:
Isn't she beautiful?
I call her Nicki.
Minaj.
Big bumper, nice headlights.
Huh? Come on, brother.
Let's boogie.
(sighs, grunts)
(engine starts)
Seat belt, buddy.
What for?
ALPHONSO (scoffs):
This for.
(engine revs, tires squeal)
("The Devil Is a Lie"
by Rick Ross playing)
♪ Whoo, whoo ♪
♪ Masterminds ♪
♪ R-O-C, double-M-G ♪
♪ Jay, I got it, I got it ♪
♪ Four stacks for the heels
On my feet ♪
♪ Car seats still smelling
Like ten keys ♪
♪ Tell the plug that
I'm lookin' for an increase ♪
♪ Wingstop
Fat boy need a ten-piece ♪
♪ Say a name
And the car start ♪
(laughing)
♪ Switching, switching ♪
♪ Lane to lane like Walmart ♪
(song ends)
(dog barking in distance)
What happened to your hands?
They're fucked up, bro.
Car crash. Engine caught fire.
(laughs) Bullshit.
I know what that is.
Too much pocket pinball, huh?
You know what I'm meaning.
But you're living the life, bro.
We're rolling with
the kings now, huh? (laughs)
They don't even see us.
They're all up there living,
and we're stuck here in this.
That's no life, bro.
So, what are you gonna do
about this, Monkey Man? Huh?
(Alphonso laughs)
(piano playing
sophisticated melody)
MAN: Bought myself a bit
of land over here down south.
You like that?
Mm-hmm.
Mate. (scoffs)
What are you doing?
That's red wine.
Yes, sir.
Well, that's a white wine glass.
(laughs)
Who is this guy, huh?
(chuckles)
Can we get somebody
over here who knows...
Tell me more
about your trip, baby.
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
I, uh...
I want to know about you.
What's this?
Little birdie?
SITA: It's a sparrow.
MAN: Want to
fly away, do you?
Queenie was right.
You are not like
the other girls.
I'll treat you like an angel.
My Indian princess.
(breathing heavily)
MAN (whispers):
We can fuck right here.
Not here, baby.
(lively, animated chatter
in Hindi)
(laughter)
(groans)
(protestors continue
shouting in Hindi)
- (rapid thumping)
- (rapid gunfire)
(grunts)
(panicked chatter)
Ma!
(shouting in Hindi)
(panicked chatter continues)
(food sizzling)
(flame whooshes)
(woman screams)
(panting)
(trembling breaths)
(dog whining)
How did you get in?
(whistles) No, no. Come.
Come, come. Good girl.
There you go.
There you go. Good girl.
You like that?
That's good. You like that?
SITA:
She'd better.
It's 4,000 rupees a plate.
(sighs heavily)
This is not the place to work
if you can't handle
that sort of stuff.
It's not a sparrow.
Your tattoo.
It's a koel.
I grew up in the forest.
Every day, I would wake up
to them singing.
(sighs)
Stop feeding that dog.
It's gonna keep coming back
expecting more.
Just gives her hope.
♪ ♪
(train whistle blows
in distance)
(gun clicking)
(dog barking nearby)
(scanner beeping)
(speaks Hindi) Next.
(Bobby whistles)
Sit. Sit. Sit.
(crowd clamoring)
ALPHONSO:
What the fuck you doing, man?
BOBBY: For the dog.
Come on, man. Let's boogie.
(grunting)
(crowd clamoring)
Sit.
(lively chatter)
REPORTER: Baba Shakti today
held a public prayer
for victims of
the ongoing land disputes,
advocating that violence
is never the answer.
Elsewhere,
the transgender inhabitants
in Yatana's northern district
have been filmed being attacked
by officers.
Chief of Police Rana Singh
assured the public
that the culprits
will be brought to justice.
(grunting)
TIGER:
You're supposed to be a monkey.
Do you know a chimpanzee
can rip a fucking
human being's face off?
Get out there and fucking
behave like a fucking beast.
- (sizzling)
- (panting)
(gunfire)
(clicks empty)
(scanner beeping)
(whirring)
Check.
(beeps, lock clicks)
(whistles)
(Bobby whistles)
(quiet chatter)
Good girl.
There you go.
(Alphonso humming)
(scatting, humming)
(snorting)
(clattering)
Where the fuck
you been, man?
I nearly finished it all
waiting for you.
You ready?
(deep, trembling breath)
Let's boogie.
(Alphonso laughs)
This guy. Come on.
(elevator bell dings)
("Redlight" by Swedish House
Mafia & Sting playing)
ALPHONSO:
Hey, Fresca.
Brought you a new boyfriend.
(Fresca chuckles)
(beeps)
Welcome to heaven, baby.
(song continues)
(lively chatter)
♪ ♪
ALPHONSO: Penthouse.
Only Queenie can go up.
Come on.
Get busy.
(whispers indistinctly)
(laughs) Mwah.
(exhales slowly)
(women moaning)
♪ ♪
♪ You don't have to put on
The red light ♪
♪ Those days are over ♪
♪ You don't have to sell
Your body to the night ♪
♪ Juicy ♪
♪ You don't have to wear
That dress tonight ♪
(speaking Hindi)
♪ Those days are over ♪
♪ You don't have to put on
The red light ♪
♪ Juicy ♪
♪ Those days are over ♪
♪ You don't have to put on
The red light ♪
(song fades)
♪ ♪
(trembling breaths)
(door opens)
(sniffs)
(sniffs, clears throat)
- (man grunts)
- (woman whimpers)
(pained grunt)
♪ ♪
(shuts off faucet)
(sniffs)
(takes deep breath, sniffs)
(yells)
(laughter)
Huh?
BOBBY: Here, sir.
("Somebody to Love" by Ben Kim
and Gorgon City playing)
Come here, baby.
(laughter)
(snorting)
(Rana moans)
♪ When the truth is found ♪
- ♪ To be lies ♪
- (laughter)
(Rana snorts, groans)
♪ And all the joy
Within you dies ♪
♪ Don't you love
Somebody to love? ♪
♪ You better find
Somebody to love ♪
(screams)
(song stops)
(coughs)
(Rana groaning)
♪ ♪
(coughing)
(Rana sniffs, grunts)
(Bobby's breath trembling)
(toilet flushes)
(grunting)
(people gasping)
(grunting and groaning)
(Rana speaking Hindi)
(continues speaking Hindi)
(groaning)
- (people screaming)
- ♪ ♪
(grunting)
(pained grunt)
(both straining)
(muffled grunting)
(panting, grunting)
Who the fuck are you,
you little rat?
(spits)
(grunting and groaning)
♪ Don't you want
Somebody to love? ♪
♪ Don't you need ♪
♪ Somebody to love? ♪
(grunting, choking)
♪ Wouldn't you love ♪
♪ Somebody to love? ♪
(people screaming)
♪ You better find
Somebody to love ♪
(grunts)
(muffled grunting)
(water burbling)
(yells)
(panting)
(exhales, mutters)
(alarm blaring)
Hey!
(yells)
(man shouting in Hindi)
♪ When the truth is found ♪
(Rana speaking Hindi)
♪ To be lies ♪
♪ And all the joy ♪
♪ Within you dies ♪
(pained yell)
♪ Don't you want ♪
♪ Somebody to love? ♪
- (shouting in Hindi)
- ♪ Don't you need ♪
♪ Somebody to love? ♪
♪ Wouldn't you love
Somebody to love? ♪
♪ You better find
Somebody to love ♪
(man shouting in Hindi)
(shouting in Hindi)
(grunting)
(alarm continues blaring)
(panting gruffly)
(yells)
♪ ♪
(panting)
(groans)
(yells)
(grunting, yelling)
(yelps, groans)
(yells)
(grunting and groaning)
♪ ♪
- (frantic shouting)
- (song ends)
(grunting, panting)
(snoring)
(grunting)
(groans)
(man shouting in Hindi
over radio)
(engine revving)
(gunfire)
- (shouting in Hindi)
- (frantic chatter)
(tires screeching)
Hey! Hey! Bobby, wait!
(tires screech)
Get in!
(speaks Hindi)
(men shouting in Hindi)
(gunfire)
Out of all the fucking cars
in there, you stole mine?
Alphonso, shut up!
(engine revs)
What the fuck
did you do, man?
Fuck! Fuck!
What were you thinking, man?
(sirens blaring)
Oh, man. Fuck, fuck.
Fuck!
OFFICER (over speaker):
Stop the vehicle now!
(gunshot)
ALPHONSO: Ah, fuck.
- What do I press?
- Put the fucking gear, brother!
(engine revving,
tires squealing)
ALPHONSO: Fuck!
(siren blaring)
(Alphonso gasps)
(both gasping)
ALPHONSO: Fuck, man!
(tires squealing)
(Alphonso whimpering)
- Duck, duck, duck, duck!
- Fuck!
Oh, fuck! Oh, fuck, man!
(gasping)
- ALPHONSO: Fuck!
- (tires squealing)
Oh! (gasping)
Fuck.
(engine revs)
(tires squealing)
ALPHONSO: Turbo! Turbo!
(whooshing)
(grunts) Fuck!
Fuck. Oh, man.
(officer speaking Hindi
over speaker)
(Alphonso whimpering)
(Alphonso groaning)
(shouting in Hindi)
(gasping)
- (shouting in Hindi)
- (Alphonso gasps)
- Did we lose them?
- Drive! Just drive!
- Look out!
- (tires screech)
(screaming)
- (woman yelling in Hindi)
- (engine revving)
(Alphonso gasps, yells)
(high-pitched ringing)
ALPHONSO (muffled):
Bobby, get up, man. Come on.
(whimpering)
I am sorry, bro.
I am sorry.
(Bobby's breath trembling)
(tires squealing)
(slow, trembling breaths)
(Bobby's breathing speeding up)
(muffled thump)
OFFICER:
Stubborn bastard, isn't he?
(laughter)
(muffled chatter)
(muffled laughter)
OFFICER (muffled): The boss
is gonna eat him alive.
- (laughter)
- He's not going to spare him.
(laughter, chatter in Hindi
growing louder)
(grunting and groaning)
(yells in pain)
- (gunshot)
- (officer shouting in Hindi)
(shouting continues in Hindi)
(grunting)
(horn honking)
(tires screeching)
(grunting)
(groaning)
(grunts) Fuck.
(panting)
(entry bell chimes)
(frantic chatter)
(siren blaring)
(panting)
(grunting)
("Ooh La La" by Bappi Lahiri
and Shreya Ghoshal playing)
(speaking Hindi)
(grunting)
(people moaning, grunting)
(chatter in Hindi)
(frantic chatter)
(grunts)
♪ Tu hai meri fantasy ♪
♪ Chhoona na, chhoona na
Chhoona na, chhoona na... ♪
You want to fuck, huh?
You want to fuck,
motherfucker, huh?
You bring the police
to my place, huh?
How dare you.
(moaning, grunting continue)
Hey. Easy.
(vicious grunting)
(people screaming)
(grunting and groaning)
♪ Haaye chhua jo toone to
Dil ne maari seeti ♪
♪ Dede in gaalon pe ek pappi
Meethi meethi ♪
♪ Ho ho chhua jo toone to
Dil ne maari seeti ♪
♪ Dede dede in gaalon
Pe ek pappi meethi meethi ♪
♪ Yauvan tera saavan bhara ♪
♪ Bheeg gaya dil yeh mera ♪
♪ Aaha toone hi barsat karaayi
Kya kare yeh yauan ♪
- ♪ Bechara bechara bechara ♪
- (whimpering)
♪ Ooh la la, ooh la la ♪
(pained yelling)
♪ Tu hai meri fantasy
Na na na ♪
♪ Chhoona na, chhoona na ♪
♪ Ab main jawan ho gayi... ♪
(yelling)
(banging against wall)
(woman screaming)
♪ ♪
(pained yelling)
(gasping)
(gun fires)
(song stops)
(shouting in Hindi)
(gunfire)
Target in sight.
- (gun fires)
- (grunts)
(muffled burbling)
♪ ♪
(birds calling)
Um...
(distorted,
indistinct whispering)
(grunting)
(whispering continues)
(yelling)
(whispering stops)
(whooshing)
(pained yelling)
- (sizzling)
- (screaming)
(sobbing, groaning)
(indistinct whispering)
♪ ♪
(whispering):
You're okay.
(birds calling in distance)
ALPHA: You're awake.
Finally.
Beautiful.
Isn't she?
Parvati and Shiva.
One half devotion,
the other destruction.
Male.
Female.
Neither.
Both.
Some people find that...
strange.
But we hijras understand it
completely.
Who are you?
I'm Alpha,
the keeper of the temple.
(grunts)
- Careful! Careful!
- (groaning)
(grunts)
(panting)
Why did you help me?
You should've died
from those injuries.
The gods must have
a greater plan for you.
We all have scars.
I should go.
No. I wouldn't do that.
The police are looking for you.
All over town.
But not here.
They find us too...
unsettling.
Stay with us.
Rest.
You need to heal.
Maybe she'll speak to you.
♪ ♪
CROWD (chanting):
Shakti! Shakti! Shakti!
Shakti! Shakti! Shakti! Shakti!
Shakti! Shakti!
♪ ♪
(footsteps approaching)
BABA SHAKTI: Who is he?
RANA: He's a nobody.
Just some crazy kid
from the gutter.
BABA SHAKTI: People once
said that about me.
RANA:
And now look at you.
You're the nation's lion.
You said he spoke of his mother.
Rana...
in the great tapestry of life,
just one small ember
can burn down everything.
The very idea of him
has to be extinguished.
Find him.
Before your nobody
becomes a somebody.
♪ ♪
The trail of destruction
started with a murder attempt
on Yatana's chief of police,
Rana Singh,
by a terrorist
posing as a member of staff.
A citywide manhunt is underway
for the terrorist
and his known associates.
Security has been raised
for the upcoming elections,
which are occurring
on the country's
most auspicious day.
(tabla music playing
in distance)
(quiet chatter)
(tabla music continues,
growing louder)
- (music ends)
- (cheering)
- Thank you.
- TABLA MAESTRO: So, uh...
(plays deep tone)
- (plays high-pitched tone)
- (laughter)
(playing deep, rhythmic tones)
(playing high-pitched,
rhythmic tones)
(laughter)
(tabla playing rapid rhythm
with deep tones)
(playing rapid rhythm
with high-pitched tones)
(laughter)
- Now they are okay.
- (playing rapid rhythm)
But...
(laughter)
And that is why
she ran away with the priest.
(laughter)
(yelps)
(laughter continues)
TABLA MAESTRO:
Funny, huh?
ALPHA:
Still can't sleep?
I never sleep.
Voices in your head?
Just one.
Her scream.
It's been inside me
my whole life.
Come with me.
(sighs)
♪ ♪
ALPHA: We were warriors before
they drove us into exile here.
The Vedas speak of a tree
that was supposedly planted
by Lord Shiva,
the destroyer of worlds.
♪ ♪
I was once like you.
A broken man.
A slave to childhood terrors.
I learned that you need
to destroy in order to grow.
To create space for new life.
Mm. Here we go.
Within its root lies
a potent toxin.
We call it Trishul
after Shiva's trident.
It will cut you open.
Only a weakened man
can benefit from this.
Only a strong man
can survive it.
Are you ready?
Yes.
(blowing)
The pain...
It will leave you once
it's finished teaching you.
(blows sharply)
(muffled flames whooshing)
(distant rumbling)
(high-pitched ringing)
(rumbling)
(monkey screeching)
♪ ♪
(indistinct whispering)
(muffled screaming)
♪ ♪
(woman yelling in Hindi)
(grunts)
(grunting)
♪ ♪
(rhythmic fluttering)
(fluttering slows)
(monkey chattering)
♪ ♪
- (people screaming)
- (blades slashing)
(bodies thudding)
(humming a tune)
(laughing evilly)
- (yells)
- (laughter)
(laughter)
(puppet show continues
in distance)
♪ ♪
(line ringing)
(phone ringing)
(phone beeps off)
(inhales)
(speaking Hindi)
- (yelling, speaking Hindi)
- (laughter)
- (rapid gunfire)
- (panicked screaming)
(rapid gunfire)
(frantic shouting)
(shouting in Hindi)
♪ ♪
(panting)
(distant gunfire)
(speaking Hindi)
(door bangs open)
♪ ♪
Huh?
(gasps)
(whimpers softly)
(Rana exhales)
(whimpering)
(Rana grunts)
(crying)
(both yell)
(Rana groans)
(yelps)
- (belt striking skin)
- (screaming)
- (woman screaming)
- (boy gasping)
(Rana shouting in Hindi)
(woman whimpering)
(Rana straining)
(woman screaming)
(Rana sighs)
(Rana grunts)
(woman gasping)
(panting)
(weak, trembling breaths)
♪ ♪
(speaking Hindi)
(yells)
(screaming)
♪ ♪
I failed her.
No.
You tried to save her.
You see scars.
I see the courage of a child
fighting to save his mother.
These are the hands of a warrior
who's destined
to challenge the gods.
All your life, you've been
fighting to feel pain.
You need to fight for a purpose.
Fight... for all of us.
It's time to remember
who you are.
REPORTER:
As the Sovereign Party
climbs in the polls,
allegations have surfaced
that you destroyed
200 acres of forestland
to build your mega factory.
It's not a factory.
It's a commune.
REPORTER:
And what about the farmers
that have been displaced?
BABA SHAKTI: Ah.
The land was barren and empty.
Few families who lived there
have joined the cause.
REPORTER:
And workers who complain
of horrible working conditions?
BABA SHAKTI:
They aren't workers.
They are my disciples.
(birds chirping)
(footsteps approaching)
(grunts)
(grunting)
(yelling)
(tabla playing
high-pitched tones)
(punching in rhythm with tabla)
(grunting)
(tabla playing stops)
(tabla playing resumes)
- (grunting)
- Yeah.
(yelling, grunting)
(speaks Hindi)
(whooping, shouting in Hindi)
Hmm.
(grunting)
Ah.
(grunting fiercely)
(onlookers whooping,
clapping in rhythm)
- (tabla playing stops)
- (cheering, applause)
(panting)
(tabla plays high-pitched tones)
(tabla playing rhythmically)
A surge of sectarian violence
has exploded around the country
after divisive remarks
made by Adesh Joshi.
International leaders
have condemned the violence
against minorities
but have stopped short
of criticizing the candidate
as he climbs in the polls.
(tabla playing rhythmically)
(laughter, jovial chatter)
(tabla continues playing
rhythmically)
(grunts)
(onlookers cheering)
(speaks Hindi)
(laughing)
(onlookers cheering)
- (laughing)
- (cheering)
ALPHA: Close your eyes,
and you will find yourself
sitting atop a mighty tree.
This is your home.
You are a beast.
Look beneath the surface,
and you will see roots
deep under the soil,
reaching far and wide.
These are the roots
of your ancestors,
the soul of your mother.
Listen to her.
You have nothing to fear.
You've been here for time.
(plays high-pitched tones)
(panting)
(crowd cheering)
ANNOUNCER:
People of Yatana...
(crowd chanting indistinctly)
(speaks Hindi) ...Baba Shakti!
CROWD (chanting):
Shakti! Shakti! Shakti!
Shakti! Shakti! Shakti! Shakti!
(chant fading):
Shakti! Shakti! Shakti!
I am nobody.
I am nothing.
I didn't choose this path.
- You chose it for me.
- (cheering)
Change never comes
without a fight.
I want you to choose
another of God's men.
He's one of us.
He is Adesh Joshi,
leader of Sovereign Party.
He will fight with us,
for us, for you.
The working man,
the poor, the sick.
Shower him with your love
and let our voice be heard
throughout the nation.
(tabla playing rhythmically)
(breathing sharply)
(grunts)
BABA SHAKTI:
They have destroyed
our sacred values.
They have stolen our homes,
poisoned our children's minds.
They have polluted us
with their symbols,
their false idols.
We have been blinded.
Will you stand with us?
Will you bleed with us?
Will you?
(crowd chanting indistinctly)
- (grunting fiercely)
- (crowd cheering)
(crowd cheering)
(both panting)
HIJRA: Lakshmi!
(whimpering)
(hijras crying)
Tell me what happened
to Lakshmi.
- Lakshmi!
- Lakshmi.
- Are you okay, Lakshmi?
What happened? What happened?
These men put a notice
on the door.
She tried to take it down,
but they beat her.
She's not breathing.
Breathe, Lakshmi, breathe.
ALPHA: Did you see?
Did you see who it was?
Shakti's men.
They said the temple
never belonged to us.
Alpha, where will we go?
If we don't have money,
they will keep doing this.
We cannot pay off some thugs.
ALPHA: We all must pray.
HIJRAS:
Lakshmi!
God has a plan.
(hijras crying)
♪ ♪
(sighs)
(takes deep breath)
(metal scrapes)
(grunts)
(siren blaring in distance)
(crowd clamoring,
chanting in Hindi)
(siren chirping)
REPORTER: We have the
election results due to break
during Diwali festival.
Sovereign Party supporters
are flooding the streets
with the party expecting
a landslide victory.
(static crackles)
("Naam Mera" by Sneha
Khanwalkar and Lazer X playing)
MAN: Baba!
CROWD: Shakti!
Baba!
Shakti!
- Baba! Baba!
- Shakti! Shakti!
Ladies and gentlemen!
♪ Jake puch le tu, puch puch
Puch, Jake puch le tu ♪
♪ Naam mera bolta mai kamm
Jyada bolta hai kaam mera ♪
Are you ready
for a fucking fight?
♪ Hai zubaan-e-gulab
Kale karam ki kitaab ♪
♪ Bhare gire jo shraab
Nasha dalta ♪
♪ Dbaav rhe tadipaar
Bhag bhag bhag ♪
♪ Na kabhi jiya
Maraa boht baar ♪
♪ Bhag bhag bhag, hai jo bhi
Dil me beta bol dal ♪
♪ Bhag bhag bhag
Hai alag mera khel ♪
Put it on the monkey.
On my left,
the still undisputed champion
of all of India,
the s-s-s-s-snake...
(crowd hissing)
King Kobra!
♪ Jyada marne ki sambhavna ♪
♪ Jeevan yeh samundar
Yaha dubaadeti hai bhavna ♪
♪ Dabte nhi usse jispe
Chlta apna davv na ♪
♪ Khaana kabhi maang na
Nahi seekha dar se bhagna ♪
(chanting):
King Kobra! King Kobra!
Okay, settle down.
(chanting continues)
Settle down, you animals.
Settle down.
(chanting dies down)
From His Majesty
all the way to the deepest,
darkest jungles
of my mother Africa...
I hunted him down.
I... (mimics gunshot)
...darted him myself,
(crowd exclaims)
and I brought him
all the way here
for your entertainment.
He's evil.
He's ferocious.
He's a dark destroyer.
I give you...
Kong!
(crowd jeering)
Do you want to see
these two animals fight?
(cheering)
The snake and the monkey.
Fight!
(chanting):
King Kobra! King Kobra!
(sniffs)
Ooh, I smell it.
- I smell it.
- (chanting continues)
(dinging)
(grunts)
(crowd gasping)
Hey.
What's going on?
(crowd chattering)
Did he fucking knock him out?
(hushed): Kobra, get up.
You get him fucking up
right now.
(kisses)
I will fuck...
Grab his arms and take him off.
(chuckles)
(microphone feedback squeals)
(clears throat)
Wow, eh?
Wow. (chuckles)
(sighs)
That was a surprise.
Fucking lucky kick, eh?
(laughs)
Looks like we got
a cheeky little monkey
on our hands tonight.
CROWD (chanting):
Kill the beast!
Kill the beast! Kill the beast!
- Ladies and gentlemen...
- (chanting continues)
I give you the biggest,
the baddest,
the bone crushing
Bhalu the Bear!
(crowd cheering)
(bell dings)
(grunting gruffly)
Fuck him up.
Fucking smash his head in, okay?
Get in there
and fucking pummel him.
(grunts)
Go. Go.
Fuck him up.
(dinging)
(grunting)
Smack him in the fucking cock!
(grunting continues)
Come on!
(cheering)
Drill him!
Drill his fucking skull in!
Drill him in the fucking face!
Go on, smack him, Bhalu!
Come on, then!
(Bhalu grunting)
(Bhalu groaning)
(crowd groaning)
Go on, Monkey Man! Yes!
(crowd chattering)
CROWD: Kill the beast!
Kill the beast!
Kill the beast! Kill the beast!
(chanting dies down)
(panting)
♪ ♪
MAN: Hail Monkey Man!
(crowd chattering)
CROWD (chanting):
Monkey Man! Monkey Man!
Monkey Man!
(chant fading): Monkey Man!
Monkey Man! Monkey Man!
♪ ♪
Alpha.
Take a look.
What is that?
There's a note.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my, my.
I mean, look at this.
Whoa.
(gasping)
Who sent us this?
Wow.
It's money.
("Siddhivinayak Aarti"
by Anuradha Paudwal playing)
♪ ♪
(announcement in Hindi
playing over speakers)
(quiet chatter in Hindi)
(cheering)
♪ ♪
Baba!
Baba! Baba!
(yells)
(cheering, whooping)
(grunting)
(laughing wildly)
CROWD (chanting):
Baba Shakti! Baba Shakti!
(crowd clamoring)
(clamoring, shouts of "Baba!")
(banging on vehicle)
(clamoring and shouts
of "Baba!" continue)
(cameras clicking rapidly)
CROWD (chanting):
Baba Shakti! Baba Shakti!
Baba Shakti!
(chanting fades)
Listen up, everyone,
if anybody fucks up tonight,
if anybody messes up,
if I get a single complaint,
I'll fuck your happiness.
Stop staring at me!
First course out right now!
It's brilliant. Very good.
(urgent, overlapping chatter)
JOSHI: Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
(applause)
Ladies and gentlemen,
what an honor it is to be here
with the Sovereign Party on the
cusp of our historic victory.
One day, the maharajas
on these walls
will be replaced with portraits
- of each and every one of you.
- (light laughter)
(drum beating rhythmically)
(crowd chanting in Hindi)
MAN: Hey, smart-ass.
Staff entrance.
(grunting and groaning)
(panting)
We will rid Mother India
of her scars
and make her beautiful
once more.
JOSHI:
I would like to acknowledge
the great contribution
of a mighty chief of police,
Rana Singh.
(cheering, applause)
His courage and integrity
has led to Yatana's
lowest crime rate.
(grunting)
(busy chatter)
Hey!
(groans)
(frantic chatter, screaming)
(grunting and groaning)
(yells)
(screams)
(grunting and groaning continue)
♪ ♪
(elevator bell dings)
(sniffs)
Oh, shit!
Shit!
(grunting and groaning continue)
("Rivers of Babylon"
by Boney M. playing)
♪ By the rivers of Babylon ♪
♪ There we sat down ♪
♪ Yeah, we wept ♪
♪ When we remembered Zion ♪
(pained grunting)
♪ There the wicked ♪
♪ Carried us away
In captivity ♪
♪ Required from us a song ♪
♪ Now how shall we sing ♪
(body thuds)
♪ The Lord's song in a... ♪
There is this one other person
without whose blessing
we would not be here.
(elevator bell dings,
doors open)
My guru.
My mentor.
His Holiness, India's lion,
- Baba Shak...
- (explosive whooshing)
- (rumbling)
- (people gasping)
(murmuring)
- (panicked chatter)
- (jingling)
(elevator whirring)
(bell dings)
(people screaming)
(groans)
(screaming continues)
(urgent chatter in Hindi)
MAN:
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Get him upstairs.
♪ ♪
- (grunting and groaning)
- (screaming continues)
(grunting)
(grunting continues)
(bell dings)
Hey! Hey!
(man shouting in Hindi)
(grunting continues)
(bell dings)
(all yelling)
(men grunting viciously)
(man speaking Hindi)
(panting)
("Dana-Dan" by Bloodywood
playing)
(song pauses)
(all yelling)
(song resumes)
(yelling, grunting and groaning)
♪ ♪
(grunting and groaning continue)
(breathing heavily)
♪ De dana dan, de dana dan
De dana dan, de dana dan ♪
♪ De, de, dem dana dan
De, de, de ♪
♪ De dana dan, de dana dan
De dana dan ♪
♪ De dana dan, de, de, de ♪
♪ De, de, de ♪
Go.
(song ends)
♪ ♪
(gunshot)
(gasps)
QUEENIE:
You motherfucker!
(Queenie shouts in Hindi)
Don't fuck with me!
I'll kill you, you bastard!
(speaking Hindi)
(shuddering breaths)
I'm gonna blow your fucking...
(Sita yells)
(thudding)
(panting)
♪ ♪
(tray clangs on floor)
(gasps)
(panting)
(yelling, grunting and groaning)
(panting heavily)
(bell dings)
♪ ♪
(door whooshing)
(chimes tinkling)
- (grunts)
- (body blow)
(groans, coughs)
(groaning)
Finally out of your tree, huh?
Get up.
♪ ♪
Did your mother
send you back for more, huh?
(grunting)
(Rana groans)
(growls)
(Rana yells)
(grunts)
(straining)
(glass clattering)
(yelling, grunting)
(grunting and groaning)
(panting)
(Rana groaning)
(Rana groans, speaks Hindi)
(both grunt)
(Rana groaning)
(shouts in Hindi)
(Rana coughs)
(wheezing)
(shoe drops to floor)
(panting)
(grunts)
(gasping)
(Rana groaning)
(muttering in Hindi)
(grunts)
(groaning)
(screaming)
(grunting)
(yells)
(panting)
♪ ♪
(beeps)
(chiming)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Welcome, Queenie.
♪ ♪
(people screaming)
(elevator chiming)
(chiming continues)
(chiming stops)
(water lapping gently)
So, you are the one?
(fireworks booming)
Look at them all.
Diwali.
The triumph of light
over darkness.
The defeat of Ravan.
But Ravan was no demon.
He was a scholar.
A visionary.
He built an empire from nothing.
Why not end
this cycle of violence?
Or we will be trapped in it
for generations.
Do you even know
my mother's name?
Do you know any of their names?
Anger will not quiet
your soul, my son.
Don't call me "son."
(scoffs softly)
(taps sandals together)
These were carved
by a devout follower
who wore them
to prevent his feet
from harming any small creature.
On the side here,
there's an old prayer:
"Forgive me, Mother Earth,
for the sin of injury
which I inflict with each step."
(helicopter approaching)
My chariot is here.
(grunts)
(squishing thud)
(grunting)
(gasping breaths)
(pained grunting)
(bones cracking)
- (yells)
- (Baba Shakti cries out)
(grunting)
(grunting viciously)
(Baba Shakti groans)
(Baba Shakti gurgling,
breathing weakly)
(weakly): You can't.
These people need me.
Please.
I'll give you what you want.
I'll do anything. (grunting)
Forgive me.
Ha-Ha-Have mercy, please.
Only God can forgive you now.
(grunts viciously)
(panting quietly)
♪ ♪
(birds chirping)
(sighs)
(laughs, gasps)
(laughing)
("Grow - A Colors Encore"
by FaceSoul playing)
- (vocalizing)
- (rhythmic tapping)
♪ Don't be afraid ♪
(vocalizing)
♪ After the darkness is light ♪
♪ So don't you be afraid ♪
(vocalizing)
♪ And there comes
The long night ♪
(vocalizing)
♪ Oh, long night ♪
♪ Have faith ♪
♪ Journey along ♪
♪ If you don't know ♪
♪ The path is long ♪
♪ But if you try ♪
♪ You'll surely grow ♪
♪ To heal past the sorrow ♪
♪ That been keeping you low ♪
♪ You low, so ♪
♪ Grow, grow, grow, grow ♪
- ♪ Grow, grow ♪
- (vocalizing)
♪ Grow, grow ♪
♪ You've got to grow ♪
- ♪ Grow, grow, grow ♪
- (vocalizing)
♪ Even if you're on your own ♪
♪ Even if you can't
Find your way ♪
♪ Even if the journey is cold ♪
♪ Believe in I to death ♪
♪ And I know
That you will grow ♪
♪ Day by day ♪
♪ If you walk with love ♪
♪ You'll never be strangers ♪
- ♪ Grow, grow ♪
- (vocalizing)
♪ Grow, grow ♪
(song ends)
♪ ♪
("The Wallet Song"
by Sneha Khanwalkar playing)
(ululating)
♪ ♪
(ululating continues)
♪ Koi toh aake dede
Koi toh aake dede ♪
♪ Koi toh aake dede ♪
One, two, three.
♪ Koi koi koi ♪
♪ Koi toh aake dede
Koi toh aake dede ♪
♪ Koi toh aake dede ♪
(vocalizing)
♪ ♪
♪ Koi toh aake dede
Koi toh aake dede ♪
♪ ♪
(song ends)
(music fades)